Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 42, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Radical Labor in the Nevada Mining Booms, 1963; Publication (Box 42, Folder 34)
    Author: Russell R. Elliott
- Box: 42, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Investigation of Jurisdictional Disputes in the Motion-Picture Industry, 1948; Publication (Box 42, Folder 35)
    Notes: December 13, 1948
- Box: 42, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Establishing a Program for Resolving Labor Disputes at Missile and Space Sites, Publication (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: The Missile Sites Labor Commission, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 36)
    Author: Wayne E. Howard
- Box: 42, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Rapport, Publication (Box 42, Folder 37)
    Author: Canada
- Box: 42, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: What Happens When the Police Strike, 1969; Publication (Box 42, Folder 38)
    Author: Gerald Clark
    Notes: November 16, 1969
- Box: 42, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Ontario Police Dispute, 1969; Publication (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Montreal Police Strike, 1969; Publication (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Box: 42, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: The Current Railway Labor-Management Dispute, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Notes: April 11, 1967
  - Item 2: Railway Labor-Management Negotiations, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Notes: April 24, 1967
  - Item 3: Settlement of the Current Railway Labor-Management Dispute, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Notes: June 12, 1967
  - Item 4: The Current Railway Labor-Management, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Notes: April 10, 1967
  - Item 5: Progress and the Railway Running Trades Unions: A Case Study, Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Author: John Lorne McDougall
  - Item 6: President's Board Views Firemen-Carrier Dispute, Publication (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Author: Association of Western Railways
- Box: 42, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Report, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Box: 42, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Temporary Prohibition of Strikes or Lockouts with Respect to the Current Railway Labor-Management Dispute, 1970; Publication (Box 42, Folder 42)
    Notes: March 4, 1970
  - Item 2: The Current Railway Labor-Management Dispute, 1970; Publication (Box 42, Folder 42)
    Notes: April 6, 1970
- Box: 42, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Labour Disputes in the USSR, Publication (Box 42, Folder 43)
    Author: Aleksandr Fastykovski
- Box: 42, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Report, 1965; Publication (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Box: 42, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Report, 1956; Publication (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Box: 42, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Government Action in the Steel Dispute of 1952, Publication (Box 42, Folder 46)
    Author: U.S. National Production Authority
    Notes: December 1, 1952
  - Item 2: The Steel Workers and the Fight for Labor's Rights, 1952; Publication (Box 42, Folder 46)
    Author: William Z. Foster
    Notes: June 1952
  - Item 3: "Little Steel" Case, 1942; Publication (Box 42, Folder 46)
    Author: U.S. National War Labor Board
    Notes: July 16, 1942
  - Item 4: The Full Facts, Publication (Box 42, Folder 46)
    Author: President's Steel Industry Board
- Box: 42, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: The Steel Labor Case of 1952, Publication (Box 42, Folder 47)
    Author: Steel Companies in the Wage Case
- Box: 42, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Report, 1966; Publication (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Box: 42, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Industrial Disputes - Selected Aspects, Publication (Box 42, Folder 49)
    Author: Louise A. Fietz
  - Item 2: Industrial Disputes and the Judicial Process, 1946; Publication (Box 42, Folder 49)
    Author: Northwestern University
    Notes: June 2, 1946
  - Item 3: Labor Relations in Relocation Centers, 1944; Publication (Box 42, Folder 49)
    Author: U.S. War Relocation Authority
    Notes: October 28, 1944
- Box: 42, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Economics Library Selections, 1961; Publication (Box 42, Folder 50)
    Author: Johns Hopkins University
- Box: 42, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The Labor Market: Freedom and Regulation, 1967; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: Richard C. Bernhard
  - Item 2: A View of the Economic Outlook from the Collective Bargaining Table, 1968; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: General Electric Company
    Notes: February 19, 1968
  - Item 3: Labor Productivity, Consumption, and Employment, 1963; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: A.J. Jaffe
    Notes: September 26, 1963
  - Item 4: Current Issues of Labour Economics in the United States of America, 1961; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Item 5: The Indian Journal of Labour Economics, 1962; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: Loyola University
  - Item 6: The Impact of Unionism, 1961; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: Norman J. Simler
  - Item 7: Landrum-Griffin Reports and Unionized Labor Market Studies, 1963; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: C.F. Smythe
    Notes: December 1963
  - Item 8: Landrum-Griffin Reports and Unionized Labor Market Studies, 1963; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Item 9: Direcciones Actuales de la Economia Laboral en los Estados Unidos, 1962; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Item 10: Unit Labor Costs in the Steel Industry, 1963; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Notes: April 23, 1963
  - Item 11: Investing in Human Capital, 1966; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: Burton A. Weisbrod
    Notes: Summer 1966
  - Item 12: The Indian Journal of Labour Economics, 1962; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: Asia Publishing House
  - Item 13: The Planned Development of Human Resources, 1963; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Notes: January 18, 1963
  - Item 14: Columbia Journal of World Business, 1966; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Item 15: Effect of High-Wage Unionized Industries on Neighboring Industries, 1962; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Item 16: The Inflation-Unemployment Tradeoff and Public Employment, 1971; Publication (Box 42, Folder 51)
    Author: U.S. Office of Economic Opportunity
- Box: 43, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labour Costs in Great Britain in 1964, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Employment and Security
- Box: 43, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Statistical Study of Wages, Prices and Employment in the Irish Manufacturing Sector, 1966; Publication (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Author: O'Herlily
- Box: 43, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Disaggregative Econometric Model of Gross Changes in Employment, 1969; Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Author: Daniel S. Hamermesh
    Notes: Fall 1969
- Box: 43, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Cost in the Puerto Rican Economy, 1950; Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Author: Simon Rottenberg
    Notes: November-December 1950
- Box: 43, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Soviet Economy, Publication (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Box: 43, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Thirteen Years in a Labor School, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: Radio Replies Press
  - Item 2: Some Problems in University Labor Education, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Alec Story, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: University of the Philippines
  - Item 4: Resident Labor Training School, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Dedication Program, 1960; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 6, 1960
  - Item 6: Trade Union Schools, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Workers' Education: What? Why? How?, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: John D. Connors
  - Item 8: Workers' Education: What? Why? How?, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: A New Frontier: Workers' Education and the University, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Workers' Education: A Challenge to Negro Colleges, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: Thomas E. Posey
    Notes: Winter 1947
  - Item 11: Unions Attitudes Towards Workers Education, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: Larry Rogin
  - Item 12: Study Abroad, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Meeting of The Committee for the Extension of Labor Education, 1946; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: The Committee for the Extension of Labor Education
    Notes: April 5, 1946
  - Item 14: University Extension and Workers' Education, 1945; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: Alfred P. Fernbach
    Notes: July 1, 1945
  - Item 15: How to Set up a Labor Institute, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: Workers Education Bureau of America
  - Item 16: Workers' Education and the Atomic Age, 1946; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Workers' Education and the Atomic Age, 1946; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education, 1948; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education
  - Item 19: Does Your University Need a Labor Institute, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: H. Fabian Underhill
    Notes: October1949
  - Item 20: Resources for Labor Education in New York City, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Box: 43, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bryn Mawr and the Workers' Education Movement, Publication (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Author: Hilda W. Smith
  - Item 2: Attempts at Evaluating Some Aspects of Labor Education and Research Service Activities, 1964; Publication (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Author: Ohio State University
- Box: 43, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Liberal Arts for Labor, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Author: Anne L. Gould
  - Item 2: Labor Education History, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Objectives and Methods in Worker Education, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Author: Wallace Wohlking
- Box: 43, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Why a Labor Extension Service Now?, Publication (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Author: The Labor Extension Service Bill
- Box: 43, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labour Education in the British Caribbean, 1959; Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Box: 43, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Cases on Union Administration, Publication (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Box: 43, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Spare-Time Education for Workers in Communist China, 1964; Publication (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Box: 43, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Study Guide: Workers' Education, Publication (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Asian Labor Education Center, Publication (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Box: 43, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Vospitanie Kommunisticheskogo Otnosheniia K Trudu, 1966; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Author: Trofim Georgievich Kallinikov
- Box: 43, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A World of New Service for You, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: The National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education
  - Item 2: A Labor Extension Service for Wage and Salary Earners, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Remarks of Elbert D. Thomas, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: Elbert D. Thomas
    Notes: June 4, 1947
  - Item 4: Labor Extension Service in the Department of Labor, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: Wayne Morse
    Notes: July 2, 1947
  - Item 5: Labor Extension Service, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: Ray J. Madden
    Notes: July 16, 1947
  - Item 6: Labor Extension Service, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Labor Education Extension Act, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: Thor C. Tollefson
  - Item 8: American Workers Want a Labor Extension Service!, 1947; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: Committee for the Extension of Labor Education
  - Item 9: Readings on Labor Education, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: The Wisconsin Idea in Workers Education, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: E.E. Schwarztrauber
  - Item 11: Workers' Education, 1934; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Author: American Association for Adult Education
    Notes: October 1934
  - Item 12: Reports of Committees, 1929; Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Notes: April 5-7, 1929
  - Item 13: Re-Proposals for Establishing a Labor Extension Service, Publication (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Box: 43, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Workers' University and Workers' Education, 1965; Publication (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Author: Mosa Pijade
- Box: 43, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Labor Under the "ISMS", 1937; Publication (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Author: Transportation Association of America
- Box: 43, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Federal Anti-Injunction Bill, 1931; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Author: Committee on Labor Injunctions
    Notes: January 1931
  - Item 2: Even Adam Had a Hearing!, 1931; Publication (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Box: 43, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Labour Inspection, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Author: Council of Europe Social Committee
- Box: 43, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Labour Inspection, 1954; Publication (Box 43, Folder 20)
    Author: The Institute for Safety and Hygiene
- Box: 43, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Canadian Labour Press from 1867: A Chronological Annotated Directory, 1948; Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Author: Robbins L. Elliott
  - Item 2: Second Class Mailing Privileges for Labor Newspapers, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Author: Arnold Weber
  - Item 3: Advertising for Labor Newspapers, Publication (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Author: Isabelle M. Zimmerly
- Box: 43, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Federal Industrial Relations Bill, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: New Labor Bill, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: Commerce Clearing House
    Notes: February 1, 1949
  - Item 3: Summary and Official Text of "Administration" Labor Relations Bill, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Notes: January 20, 1949
  - Item 4: Report of Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Notes: March 21, 1949
  - Item 5: Texts Concerning Early Labour Legislation, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: C.W. De Vries & J. De Vries
  - Item 6: Observations on the Labor Policy Proposals of the National Association of Manufacturers, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: National Lawyers Guild
  - Item 7: Aide-Memoire de Legislation du Travail Malgache, 1966; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: Ancien Ministre du Travail
    Notes: July 1, 1966
  - Item 8: Industrial Conciliation Amendment, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: Southern Rhodesia
  - Item 9: East Pakistan Factories Act, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: Law of Tea Estates Maternity Benefit & Plantation Employees Provident Fund, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: East Pakistan Shops & Establishments Act, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: East Pakistan Trade Unions Act, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Item 13: Summary of Orders and Regulations, 1971; Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: British Columbia Board of Industrial Relations
    Notes: February 1, 1971
  - Item 14: The Development and Current Application of Missouri Public Sector Labor Law, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: Francis J. Loevi
  - Item 15: Protective Labor Legislation in Indiana, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: Jay B. Kennedy, Danilo Orescanin
  - Item 16: Native Employment Ordinance, Publication (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Author: Papua-New Guinea
- Box: 43, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labour Relations Act, 1973; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: British Columbia
    Notes: December 15, 1972
  - Item 2: Lag om Kollectivavtal, Arbetsdomstol, Statlig Lonegaranti Vid Konkurs, Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: Tidens Forlag
  - Item 3: May Day 1967, Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: Ceylon Ministry of Labour, Employment and Housing
  - Item 4: Review of Labour Legislation in Pakistan, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: East Pakistan Employment of Labour, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: Bureau of Labour Publications
  - Item 6: East Pakistan Inland Water Transport, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Guide Juridique de Poche, 1966; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: La Vie Ouvriere
  - Item 8: Protective Labor Legislation in Indiana, Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: Jay B. Kennedy & Danilo Orescanin
  - Item 9: The Law of Conditions of Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Alaska Administrative Code, 1970; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Author: Alaska Department of Labor
    Notes: June 1970
  - Item 11: West Pakistan Industrial Disputes Ordinance, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: West Pakistan Trade Unions Ordinance, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 13: West Pakistan Industrial & Commercial Employment, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: West Pakistan Industrial & Commercial Employment, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Item 15: The Labour Relations Act, 1970; Publication (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Box: 43, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Your Native Workers and the Law, 1958; Publication (Box 43, Folder 24)
    Author: D.B.H. Grobbelaar
- Box: 43, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Road Passenger Transportation Trade, Witwatersrand and Pretoria, 1962; Publication (Box 43, Folder 25)
    Author: South Africa Legislature
    Notes: July 20, 1962
  - Item 2: Road Passenger Transportation Trade, Witwatersrand and Pretoria, 1962; Publication (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Box: 43, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws and their Administration, Publication (Box 43, Folder 26)
    Author: The Alabama Department of Labor
- Box: 43, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Fallos Plenarios del Trabajo, Publication (Box 43, Folder 27)
    Author: Enrique Fernandez Gianotti
  - Item 2: Reglamentacion De Asociaciones Profesionales de Trabajadores, 1963; Publication (Box 43, Folder 27)
    Author: Argentine Republic
- Box: 43, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws of the State of Arizona, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
    Author: Arizona Labor Department
  - Item 2: Labor Laws of the State of Arizona, 1963; Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
    Notes: 1962-1963
  - Item 3: State of Arizona Labor Laws, Publication (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Box: 43, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: An Annoted Digest of the Labor Laws of the State of Arkansas, Publication (Box 43, Folder 29)
    Author: Arkansas Department of Labor
- Box: 43, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Conciliation and Arbitration Act, 1971; Publication (Box 43, Folder 30)
    Author: Australia Ministry of Labour and National Service
    Notes: December 7, 1971
- Box: 43, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Arbeitsrecht in der Betrieblichen Praxis, Publication (Box 43, Folder 31)
    Author: K. Myrhofer
  - Item 2: Die Grundrechte mit Arbeitsrechtsbeziehung und die Neufassung des Osterreichischen Grundrechtskataloges, Publication (Box 43, Folder 31)
    Author: Robert Walter & Gerhard Schnorr
  - Item 3: Short Review of Social and Working Conditions of Employed Persons in Austria, 1963; Publication (Box 43, Folder 31)
    Author: Osterreichischer Gewerkschaftsbund
    Notes: January 1, 1963
- Box: 43, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Le Contrat de Travail Le Contrat D'Emploi, 1967; Publication (Box 43, Folder 32)
    Notes: November 1967
- Box: 43, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: General Labor Legislation, 1961; Publication (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Bibliography: Labor Management Relations Act, 1947, as Amended by the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959, Publication (Box 43, Folder 33)
    Author: Sylvia H. Washington